乔伊  你在吗
Joey? Are you in there?
-是瑞秋  -乔伊  你得跟她谈一谈
- That's Rachel. - Joey, you have to talk to her.
不行  经过那晚的事之后
No. I can't. I can't. Not after the other night.
感觉太奇怪了
It's too weird, okay?
别告诉她我在这里
Don't tell her I'm here.
别吃那个
Don't eat that!
-瑞秋  -乔伊在吗
- Hey, Rachel. - Is Joey here?
-我没有看到他  你呢  -没有
- I don't see him. Do you see him? - I don't see him.
或许他在糖碗里  乔伊  没人
Maybe he's in the sugar bowl. Joey? Nope.
至少你们能彼此逗乐
Well, at least you make each other laugh.
-怎么了  -自从他那晚跟我坦白之后
- What's up? - I haven't seen him since that night
我就一直没见过他
that he told me how he, you know...
我觉得他在躲我
I don't know, I think he's avoiding me.
为什么地板上会有百吉饼
Why is that bagel on the floor?
-我们在玩游戏  -钱德勒脱了衣服玩的吗
- We were playing a game.- Was Chandler naked?
像是套圈圈之类的游戏吗
Sort of like a ring-toss kind of situation?
-没错  -什么  不是
- Sure! - What? No! No!
好吧  如果你们看到乔伊
All right, listen. If you see Joey,
能不能告诉他...
will you just tell him that...?
告诉他我很想他
Tell him I miss him.
好吧  你听到了吗
Okay. Did you hear that?
是啊  裸体百吉饼游戏
Yeah. That naked bagel game?
我很怀疑  这个洞很小的
Dude, I don't know. That's a pretty small hole.
-你得跟她谈一谈  -我做不到
- Honey, you've gotta talk to her. - I can't.
你们不知道真情告白之后
You guys don't know what it's like
却被拒绝的感觉有多难受
to put yourself out there like that and just get shot down.
我不知道那种感觉
I don't know what that's like?
我在25岁前一直以为
Until I was 25, I thought the response
对"我爱你"的回应是"真糟糕"
to "I love you" was "Oh, crap."
我没有被拒绝过
No rejection?
我连在减肥营都被拒绝过
I got shot down at fat camp.
天啊  饿肚子的孩子可真恶毒
Boy, kids are mean when they're hungry.
我该怎么办
So, what do I do?
她是瑞秋  难道你永远都不跟她说话了吗
This Rachel. You're gonna never talk to her again?
那很奇怪  也很尴尬  但至少你得试试看
I know it's weird and it's awkward, but you gotta at least try.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
我忘了这个曾套在你的...
I almost forgot this was on your...
我们根本就没玩
We didn't play it!
等你们喝完茶之后
Okay, so when you're done with your tea,
我可以看茶叶帮你们算命
I'll look at the leaves and tell your fortune.
-你会茶叶算命法吗  -我做过好几年了
- You didn't know read tea leaves? - I've done it for years.
我后来放弃是因为我算得太难了
I actually stopped because I was so accurate.
生命最大的乐趣之一
And one of the great joys of life...
就在于其神奇的不可预测性
...is its wondrous unpredictability, you know?
而且我喝茶会拉肚子
And also, tea tends to give me the trots.
-我喝完了  帮我算吧  -好的
- Okay. I'm done. Read mine. - Okay.
我看到一个梯子
I see a ladder.
代表的要么是升职  要么是暴力性死亡
Which can mean either a promotion or a violent death.
我是主厨  不可能再升职了
I'm the head chef. I can't get promoted.
下一个是谁
Who's next?
-我喝完了  帮我算  -好吧
- Okay. I'm done. Do mine. - Okay.
好吧  我看到一个圈圈
Oh! Okay, I see a circle.
那表示你要么怀了孩子
Which can either mean you're having a baby...
要么会做出科学发现
...or you'll make a scientific discovery!
我确实经常在实验室待着
Well, I have been spending a lot of time in the lab.
你的茶叶又预示着什么呢  菲比
What does yours say, Pheebs?
好吧
All right.
我会认识一个男人  而且很快
Oh, I'm gonna meet a guy! And really soon!
他会是我的梦中情人
He's gonna be the man of my dreams.
或许不是我昨晚梦到的那个男人
Probably not the guy I had a dream about last night.
有人看到我的衬衫吗
Has anyone seen my shirt?
是前开式的淡鲑鱼色衬衫
It's a button-down, like a faded salmon color?
你是说那件粉红色衬衫吗
You mean your pink shirt?
淡鲑鱼色
Faded salmon color?
不  我没看到你的粉红色衬衫
No, I haven't seen your pink shirt.
我一定把它落在蒙娜家了  我就知道
Great. I must have left it at Mona's. I knew it!
你可以到安·泰勒的专卖店再买一件
I'm sure you can get another one at Ann Taylor's.
那是我最爱的衬衫  我超喜欢
That's my favorite shirt. I love that shirt.
那就让蒙娜还给你啊
Just ask Mona to give it back.
我不知道  或许可以吧
I don't know. I guess could.
只是我们最后闹得不太愉快
It's just we didn't really end things on such good terms.
如果我去她家
And if I went over there,
就等于无视她分手时对我提出的唯一要求
I'd be ignoring the one thing she asked me to do when we broke up.
她要我去跳楼自杀
Jump up my own ass and die.
等一下
Oh, wait a second, you guys?
这几周以来
For the last couple weeks,
我走到哪里都会看到那个男人
I've been seeing that guy everywhere I go.
我们搭同一班公车  去同一家书店
We take the same bus, we go to the same bookstore,
同一家干洗店  或许他就是我的真命天子
and the same dry cleaners. Maybe he's the tea guy.
菲比  你们看到了吗
Phoebe, did you see that?
他绝对是在打量你  而且他超帅的
He totally checked you out! And he is so cute!
我的茶叶像是乡巴佬  那是什么意思
Mine is a picture of the Village People. What does that mean?
菲比喝茶会拉肚子
Tea gives Phoebe the trots!
我以为乔伊跟我待在一起就不会尴尬了
I thought Joey and I would be okay once we hung out,
但现在我们都不知道该怎么相处
but it's like we don't even know how to be with each other any more.
虽说你们现在很难相处  但情况会改善的
I konw, it's tough now, but things will get better.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
如果情况不断恶化...
What if it gets worse and worse and worse,
我们都无法共处一室了该怎么办呢
to the point where we can't be in the same room with each other?
我不善于给人提建议
I'm not great at the advice.
我能讽刺你一番吗
Can I interest you in a sarcastic comment?
要奶酪吗
Some cheese?
老公  为什么布鲁斯·史普林斯汀的CD
Honey, why is the Bruce Springsteen CD
会放在凯特·史帝文斯的盒子里
in the Cat Stevens case?
如果我找不到正确的盒子
Let's just say if I can't find the right CD case,
我就会随手拿个盒子来装
I just put it in the nearest one.
那凯特·史帝文斯的CD在哪里
Okay. Where is the Cat Stevens CD?
在詹姆士·泰勒的盒子里
In the James Taylor case.
-那张CD在哪里  -我帮你节省些时间吧
- Where is James Taylor CD? - Honey, I'll save you some time.
那200张CD没有一张是放在正确盒子里的
Two hundred CDs, not one of them in the right case.
好吧  不需要慌张  大家深呼吸
Okay. No need to panic. Deep breaths, everyone.
我们只需要花些时间
Okay, we're just gonna have to spend some time
把CD放在正确的盒子里
and put the CDs in the right cases.
如果要整理的话  那就应该按某种顺序排好
If we do that, we should come up with some kind of order.
按字母顺序或音乐风格
You know, alphabetically or by genre?
我不知道  这件事我们得好好商量
I don't know. We have to talk this through.
天啊  你们有什么毛病啊
Oh, my God, you guys have such problems!
我真为你们感到难过
I feel so terrible for you!
好吧  对不起
All right. Okay, I'm sorry.
你和乔伊两个人满脑子
Look, you and Joey, you're both focusing
都是这件烦人的事
on this uncomfortable thing.
你们需要改变一下话题
What you need to do is to change the subject.
下次见面  跟他谈谈别的事情
Next time you see him try to get him talking about something else.
对  那挺有道理的
Yeah, that makes sense.
或许你在工作上有问题
Yeah. I don't know, maybe you have a work problem
需要他的建议...
that you need his advice on.
-我可以用这招  -很好
- I could do that. - Good.
你连迈阿密天龙的原声带都有吗
Honey, the Miami Vice soundtrack? Really?
那只是唱片行的赠品
They were just giving those away at the store.
我得拿钱去换
In exchange for money.
我真的不知道该给你什么建议  瑞秋
I really don't know what to tell you, Rach, I really don't.
或许乔伊可以帮你解决工作上的这个大问题
Maybe Joey could help you out with your big work problem.
-什么  -对  乔伊  她...
- What? - Yeah, Joey, she's...
瑞秋工作上碰到一个大问题
Rachel's got this big work problem.
真的很伤脑筋
It is a head-scratcher.
我们想赶上晚餐预约
You know what? If we're gonna make dinner,
就得马上出发了
we're gonna have to leave.
你工作上出了大问题
So you have a big work problem?
对  那是...
Yeah. It's, uh...
Yeah, it's, uh...
真的没什么
You know, it's nothing.
好吧
Okay.
我想我该走了
So I think I'm gonna take off.
不  乔伊  等等  我确实有问题
No, wait, Joey, it is. It's something. It's...
是我的老板
It's my boss.
-是吗  -对  跟...
- Yeah? - Yeah. And, uh...
跟我的宝宝
And my baby.
是吗
Yeah?
我老板想买我的宝宝
My boss wants to buy my baby.
什么  我的天啊
What? Oh, my God!
我跟你说过了  这真的是个大问题
I know, I told you, it's a really big problem!
-他要买你的宝宝  -你能相信吗
- He wants to buy your baby? - Can you believe that?
-那太疯狂了  -我就是那么跟他说的
- That's crazy. - That's what I told him!
-怎么会发生这种事  -我会告诉你的
- How did this even happen? - Well, I'll tell you.
我老板跟他太太  他们不孕  所以...
See, my boss and his wife, they can't have children, so...
我们在圣诞派对上碰了面...
And then when we were at the Christmas party...
他喝醉了  跟我说
...he got drunk and said to me,
"瑞秋  我要买下你的宝宝"
"Rachel, I want to buy your baby."
天啊
Man!
你说问题出在老板跟宝宝身上的时候...
When you said it was a problem about your boss and the baby...
我以为你是指产假的问题
...I figured it was about maternity leave.
对啊
Yeah.
对  那样子问题就简单多了
Yeah, that would have been a much simpler problem.
-你好  -是你  我走到哪里都会碰到你
- Oh, hello. - Oh, it's you. I see you everywhere.
我是吉米  吉米·尼尔森
I'm Jim. Jim Nelson.
嗨  吉米  吉米·尼尔森
Hi, Jim-Jim Nelson.
我是菲比  菲比·布非
I'm Phoebe-Phoebe Buffay.
我们最近经常见面
We certainly have been seeing a lot of each other lately.
没错  或许明天晚餐时
We have. Maybe we'll be seeing each other
我们也能碰面  八点可以吗
at dinner tomorrow night, say around 8 o'clock?
我们或许会碰面吧
Well, maybe we will.
蒙娜
Mona?
如果我是件鲑鱼色衬衫  我会在哪里呢
Okay, if I were a salmon shirt, where would I be?
抱歉  我把酒洒到你的衬衫上了
I am so sorry I spilled wine all over your shirt.
-没关系  -不  还是湿的
- It's okay. - No, it's still wet.
我拿去洗干净  免得留下印子
Let me get it out before it sets.
我这里有件衣服你可以穿
I have something you could wear.
拿去吧
Here.
我真的不想穿女式衬衫
I don't know if I want to wear a woman's shirt.
-那是男式衬衫  -可怕的粉红色
- No, no, that's a man's shirt. - Awfully pink.
那不是粉红色
It's not pink!
天啊  老婆  我们注定要在一起
Oh, my god. Honey, we are so meant to be together.
我们都有安妮的原声带
Look, we both have the copies of Annie soundtrack.
老公  两张都是你买的
Honey, both yours.
谢谢你给我关于乔伊的建议
Hey, great advice on that Joey thing.
工作的问题吗
Yeah? The work problem?
感觉太棒了
It was perfect.
我又在他身上找回了朋友的感觉
It really felt like he was my friend again.
你说你遇到了什么问题
What problem did you say you have?
那不重要
Oh, that's not important.
重点是我觉得一切都会没事
The point is, I really... I think everything's gonna be okay.
需要我效劳吗
May I help you?
你觉得你可以随便买走我朋友的宝宝吗
You think you can just buy my friend's baby?
我们一直巧遇  真是有缘啊
Isn't it funny how we kept running into each other?
就像是有人想把我们撮合到一起
It's as if someone really wants us to be together.
没错  那就是我
Someone does. Me.
聪明的家伙  做得好
Witty banter. Well done.
-不错  -跟我谈谈你自己
- Good. - So tell me a little bit about yourself.
好吧  我是按摩师
Okay. I'm a masseuse.
我以前在这个地方工作
And I used to work at this place...
你喜欢参加派对吗
Do you like to party?
我喜欢派对
I like parties.
你很狂野  对吧
You're wild, aren't you?
对  我猜是有一点
Yeah, I guess. A little.
那没有什么  我也很狂野
Ain't no thing. I'm wild too.
总之...
So anyway...
我住在纽约  生活方式有点狂野
...I've lived in New York, somewhat wildly, I guess...
我从14岁就住在这里
...for, well, since I was 14.
抱歉我盯着你不放
I'm sorry. I'm staring.
因为你有双非常漂亮的眼睛
It's just that you have the most beautiful eyes.
-别说了  -还有你的胸部
- Oh, stop it. - And your breasts!
好吧
Okay.
听着  你的攻势有点太猛了
Look, you're coming on a little strong.
但我暂且认为你没有恶意
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
因为宇宙中有股力量将我们牵引到一起
Because since the universe really wants us to be together.
我们为何不重新来过呢
So why don't we start over?
你可以跟我谈谈你自己
You can tell me about yourself.
-好吧  -好吧
- All right. - Okay.
我写给小孩子看的...
I write erotic novels...
色情小说
...for children.
-什么  -我的书非常不受欢迎
- What? - They're wildly unpopular.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
有件事你可能会感兴趣  我是个博士
Also, you might be interested to know that I have a Ph.D.
真的吗
Wow! You do?
-对  我的老二超大  -够了
- Yep. A pretty huge... - All right.
明天太阳将会升起
The sun'll come out...tomorrow! Bet...
拿全部家当打赌
your bottom dollar that tomorrow...
明天会是晴天
There'll be sun.
乔伊  听我说  谢谢你昨天
Joey, honey, listen. Thank you for talking to my yesterday
陪我聊我老板的问题  那对我来说意义重大
about that thing with my boss. That really means a lot.
别客气  我得告诉你
Not a problem. Just so you know...
那家伙不会再为了宝宝的事来烦你了
...that guy won't be bothering you about that baby thing anymore.
-什么  -就说我已经帮你解决了
- What? - Let's just say I took care of it.
我们得谈一谈
Let's say more.
别担心  我平心静气地跟他谈过
Don't worry. Don't worry. I just told him, very nicely:
"你不能随便买别人的宝宝  放弃吧"
"You don't go buying people's babies! So back off!"
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
不要啊
No, no, no!
乔伊  他不想买我的宝宝  那是我编出来的
Joey, he doesn't want to buy my baby! I made that up!
什么  为什么
What? Why?
那样我们才有话题可聊嘛
So we would have something to talk about!
才不会显得尴尬
So it wouldn't be awkward!
你想不出来别的借口吗
And you couldn't think of anything else?
你说你老板要买你的宝宝
You said your boss wants to buy your baby?
真不敢相信你对我老板大叫
I can't believe you yelled at my boss!
我会被开除  我该怎么办
I'll lose my job! What am I gonna do?
你可以卖掉你的宝宝
You could always sell your baby.
我不敢相信你会去找我老板
Joey, I can't believe you brought my boss into this!
我会被开除的
I'll be fired!
-你骗我  -是她要我那么做的
- You lied to me! - Well, she told me to!
钱德勒有两张安妮的原声带
Chandler has two copies of Annie!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
-罗斯  -你们好啊
- Ross! - Hello!
罗斯  你在这里干什么
Ross, what are you doing?
我没在自摸
Not touching myself,
希望你们听了能放心一点
if that makes anyone less uncomfortable.
早安  您找我吗
Morning. You wanted to see me?
请进  坐下
Please, come in. Have a seat.
听着  佐纳先生
Look, Mr. Zelner...
-让我先说吧  -好吧
- I think it's best that I speak first. - Yeah.
我请了人事部的李
I've asked Lee from human resources to be here
作为我们谈话的见证人
as a witness to our conversation.
天啊
Oh, God.
如果我有暗示过你
If I in any way
我想买你的宝宝...
implied that I wanted to buy your baby...
我很抱歉  好吗
...I am sorry. Okay?
上星期我问你  你的预产期是什么时候
Last week, when I asked you when your due date was...
我并没有暗示你
...I certainly did not mean that
我想"买"你的宝宝
I felt that I was "due" your baby.
我希望清楚地告诉你...
I want to be very clear...
我了解  那是你的宝宝
...that I understand that it's your baby...
我不能买下它
...and it is not mine to purchase.
只要把话说清楚就好了
Well, as long as we are clear about that.
到了
There it is.
-这不是你常去的洗衣店  -我知道
- That's not your regular cleaners. - I know.
但和我约会的那个怪胎会去那里
but that creep that I went on that date with goes to there,
我得找家新的洗衣店
so I have to find a new one.
我还得找新的音像店
I also have to find a new video store,
银行  成人书店  杂货店...
a new bank, a new adult bookstore, a new grocery store...
-什么  -新的杂货店
- What? - A new grocery store.
宇宙预示我会认识一个好男人
The universe said I'd meet a nice guy.
结果就给我这么一个货色
And that's what they gave me?
我上天堂后  一定要痛扁某人
When I get up there, I'm gonna kick some ass.
别着急  菲比  你会遇到梦中情人的
Don't worry Phoebe, You'll meet someone.
如果我能找到好男人  你也可以
If I can meet a great guy, so can you.
对  我们都可以  也都会找到的
Yeah, we both can. And we both will.
-你不必进来  -开什么玩笑
- You didn't have to come in with me. - Are you kidding?
这里是给衣物去污的地方
This is where they get out stains.
对我来说这就像是迪士尼乐园
This is like Disneyland for me.
我要到这里欣赏干净的衬衫跳舞
I'm gonna be over here watching the dance of the clean shirts.
对不起  你掉了...
Excuse me. I think you dropped...
-哇  -怎么了
- Wow! - What?
抱歉  你真的是美得不可思议
I'm sorry. It's just that you're so incredibly beautiful.
我也这么觉得  但又能怎么办呢
Well, I'm sorry about that too. But what are you gonna do?
希望你别觉得我疯了
I hope you don't think I'm crazy,
我觉得帮你捡东西算是命中注定
but I feel like I was meant to pick this up,
-你相信那种事吗  -有一点
- Do you believe in that kind of thing? - A little.
你终于靠谱了
Now you're talking.
你想去喝杯咖啡吗
Would you like to go out and have a cup of coffee?
我很乐意  我去跟我朋友打个招呼
I'd love to. Let me tell my friend.
是墨水印子  我能看你把它洗干净吗
An ink stain! Can I watch how you get this out?
她一定是先走了
She must have left.
-所以呢  发生了什么事  -没事了
- So? What happened? - It's all gonna be okay.
他们很高兴我不会告他们
They're so happy I'm not suing them,
我还能多放一个月的带薪产假
that they gave me one extra month paid maternity leave.
只要我明白那些薪水
So long as I understand the money
并不是购买这个宝宝
should not be construed as a down payment
或其他宝宝的订金
on this or any other child that I may bear.
拉夫罗兰真的想尽办法...
Ralph Lauren is going out of their way
要证明他们不是贩婴集团
to show they're not in the baby-buying business.
钱德勒  能让我们独处一下吗
Chandler, can you give us a minute?
你这是要把我踢出自家客厅吗
Oh I'm sorry, you're kicking me out of my own living room?
对
Yeah.
我去里面待着
I'll be in there.
乔伊  抱歉我骗了你
Joey, I'm really sorry I lied to you.
我只是希望解决我们...
I was just trying to make things...
我知道
I know. I know.
这个方法的确有效
It kind of worked.
我不知道你是怎么想的
I mean, you know, I don't know about you,
但出了这档子事之后  我就没想过咱们的问题
but I haven't thought about our thing since all this.
对  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
对  我们又恢复了"朋友"的样子
Yeah. It's kind of been like "us" again, a little bit.
-对啊  我很想念那段时光  -我也是
- Yeah, I know. I've missed that. - Me too.
我也没再去想  自己对你敞开心扉
I haven't thought about how I put myself out there...
跟你说过那些话  你跟我的感觉不同
and said that stuff. How you didn't feel the same way about me
还有这一切有多尴尬
and how it was really awkward.
我的妇产科医生想杀我
My gynecologist tried to kill me.
编号是J437-A
Item J437-A.
颜色  冬莓色
Color: Winterberry.
进来吧
Hi, listen. Come here. Come...
关于昨天的事我很抱歉
I'm so, so sorry about yesterday.
我真的很抱歉  那只是...
I'm really, really sorry. It's just...
听着  罗斯  你不必道歉
Listen, Ross, you don't have to apologize.
我知道你为什么会跑去我家
I understand why you were there.
-真的吗  -对  你还对我有感觉
- You do? - Yeah. You still have feelings for me.
老实说  我对你也还有感觉
To be honest, I still have feelings for you, too.
我希望我们能复合  但那是不可能的
I wish we could work it out, Ross, but we can't.
你跟瑞秋还有宝宝的事太复杂了
It's too complicated with you and Rachel and the baby.
我只是...
I just...
我们并不属于彼此
It just wasn't meant to be.
天啊  你说得对
Oh, God. You're right.
罗斯  我们得坚强
Ross, we have to be strong.
好吧  我得走了
Okay, I'm gonna go.
我能留这件衣服来怀念你吗
Can I? To remember you?
不行
No.